[{"answer": "I know. Oh, I know.  I've been calling all morning. Oh, you have no idea. Miss my friend, they're so difficult to get, really they are. We get them from that place, you know, when they're just little chicks, and then we have to..", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Certainly not. Oh, no. Certainly not. This will be a full grown myna bird. Full grown", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes. I understand there are different varieties, it that true", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "These are for my sister... her birthday you see. As she'll be eleven and... well, frankly, I wouldn't want a pair of birds that were too demonstrative", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I think so, sir.  Now then, let me see", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, sir, those are... redbirds", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " Yes, we call them that too.  Ahhh, here we are, Lovebirds...", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " Doesn't what make me...", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yes, that's a particularly dangerous time", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Some of them are", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "How", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "We never met in court or anyplace else", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We met in court", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "That's true. I'll rephrase it. I saw you in court", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Yes. Yes, someone's got to feed them", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "The Brenners? Mr. and Mrs. my friend", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "The two kids", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yep", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The little my friend girl", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " The little my friend girl", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " It's my friend, ain't it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " my friend", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " No, it's my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " It's my friend, ain't it", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " It's my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Yes? Who is it", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Who's me", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Didn't you see the lovebirds", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "To bring your sister those birds. You said it was her birthday. Besides, I was coming up anyway", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Can't see a thing", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "But you were coming up anyway, remember", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend... my friend may have made other plans. I'll have to see. Besides, I can find my own way", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I'm sure", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I don't think so.  I have to get back to that place", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Darling, of course I do", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Don't you like us", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Don't you like my friend", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " Darling, of course I do", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I don't know yet", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I think I can handle my friend by myself", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I know exactly what I want, my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yes, I was lying", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "You were lying", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Did you really write a letter to me? Or was that a lie, too", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Because it seemed stupid and foolish", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "I told you what happened in that place", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "You needn't worry. It's over and done with. A long time ago", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Isn't there?  Maybe there isn't. Maybe there's never anything between my friend and any girl", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Different", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " A trifle", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Someone ought to tell her she'd be gaining a daughter", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "What about my friend? Didn't he have anything to say about this", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "He wants me to go to my friend's party tomorrow afternoon.  I said I would", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "It seems so pointless.  I think I'll go to sleep. This has been a busy day.  My luggage", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Do you think I should go", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "It's really up to my friend, isn't it", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I really shouldn't have any more. I'm a little tipsy already", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I couldn't possibly. I have to get back", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "I couldn't possibly. I have to get back", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "Cheers", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Well... I have to get to work tomorrow morning, for one thing", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": " I have several jobs", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": " I have several jobs", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "I do different things on different days", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Nothing.  I go to bird shops on Fridays", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Do you know what I was doing in that shop", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": " It's an uprising", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Certainly, of birds", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "Because my son is...  My son seems to be fond of you.  And I...  I'm not quite sure how I feel about it. I really don't know if I... like you or not", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "Yes, I think so. My son is important to me. I want to like any girl he chooses", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so. My son is important to me. I want to like any girl he chooses", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": " Then I don't suppose it'll matter much to anyone but me", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "What were the crows after at the school", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "my friend. I think they were after the children", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "They are incapable of organized warfare", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "I have seen jays doing everything it is conceivable for jays to do. Ornithology happens to be my avocation, my friend. You're talking about preservation of the species, a hen protecting her young. There's a vast difference between..", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "All this shouting", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "A war? Against who? Did the Russians...", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": " I don't know, honey", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "I wish I could say. But if I could answer that, I could also tell you why people are trying to kill people", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "They're gone. The same pattern", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "We won't be here", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "If...  If... when we get to that place...  If they're already there", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "If they are", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "We'll worry about that when we get there", "docId": "Birds_-The.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "What do we have to know, my friend? We're all together, we all love each other, we all need each other. What else is there? my friend, I want us to stay alive", "qsentId": 88}]